Register of the Eric Voegelin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographs and Postcards, 1920s-1981, undated
  - Negatives and prints, circa 1920s
    - Packet 11, negatives
      - Street scene (Box-folder 135: 382-383)
    - Original housing for negatives (Box-folder 133: 6)
- Incremental Card File, undated
  Address, research, and bibliographic index cards.
  - Address cards, undated (Box 136)
  - Bibliographical index cards, arranged alphabetically by author, undated (Boxes 137, 139)
    Includes index cards listing Voegelin's writings and reviews. Inventory #393
  - Index research cards, undated (Box 140)
- Not yet described (Box 138)